Defeating the Heli-Tornado
What?!
You were just bluffing?!
Yeah! I just said the first thing that came to mind.
But why would you do that?
Oh yeah?! Well, I have a secret weapon that can beat your Heli-Tornado! (FX-italic)
Why did you have to say that?!
It was the only way to get out of that situation...
Juuun!
Don't worry. I'll think of a plan starting now.
What are you two talking about?
Vera?
It's none of your business.
Oh, really?
I think it is.
Aah!
Here's the thing.
We were filming a dance video by the Mowtown docks yesterday.
When robots came out of nowhere and started fighting, I quickly got out my camera.
And that's when I saw two familiar faces.
Care to explain?
Uhh... maybe they were guys that just look like us?
That's right! They say there are at least three people in the world that look exactly like you!
Wearing the same clothes, with the same hair, and the same shoes?!
You expect me to buy that story?! Really?!
We're late for something!! Gotta go!
Hey! Get back here!
What do we do? We can't keep running away from them!
We just have to figure out a way to steal that video from Vera!
Well... she could have saved other copies.
And if she uploads it to the Internet, there's nothing we can do at that point.
Don't worry about a thing! I have a great idea!
That just makes me worry more...
Good day, everyone.
I would like to address the rumors going around regarding a giant robot.
Giant robot?
Yes!
There have been reported sightings of robots in
concrete channels, under highways, and flying above the city,
so we would like to reveal the truth about all these robots!
I'm intrigued right now!
Tune in to our live broadcast this evening at 8!
Remember to subscribe to our channel!
What do you think he's going to say, huh?
Could it be about that robot we saw before?
You think?
- Oh no, he got us!
- What?
Going live at 8 today?! Tch!
That dweeb is trying to sabotage the video we took of the robots!
So tell me, what do we do next?
I'll start thinking about that now.
Not this again!
Jun! It's all set up.
Woah...
That's awesome! Wow!
It's a jet engine from a plane.
It's been modified so its wind will be strong enough to blow over a Metal Cardbot.
You're the best, Uncle Edo! This is great!
Can't you call me your bro?! I'm not that old!
But, what are you planning to do with this?
It's for special training! So you can learn how to defeat Shadow X's tornado!
Aha! Good idea!
Let me have a go at it!
Metal Breath, pickup!
Mega Trucker, setup!
Alright, alright! Let's do this!
Okay, setting power to 80%.
Mega Trucker will be harder to blow away since he's heavier than Blue Cop, right?
I can handle a little spring breeze.
Power 100%.
Mega Trucker, use your Shoulder Shield! You gotta hang on!
Shoulder Shield!
Output 120%!
I'm not backing down yet!
Keep it up, Mega Trucker!
This is sure to work against Shadow X!
Shadow X!
So you guys are training? Should've let me know! I would have helped you!
Augh, this is a rental!
You'll pay for the damages!
Not my problem!
Shall we settle the score once and for all?
Mega Trucker, show us what you got!
That blockhead from yesterday, huh? Ha!
Spinning Cutter!
Look out, Mega Trucker!
Hahaha! You thought I'd attack from the front where you have your defenses?
Are you really that stupid?
I'm not done yet!
Oh? Persistent, aren't you?
Gotcha!
Let go of me!
Wait-!
You broke my propeller!
Come back, Mega Trucker!
You fought hard, Mega Trucker. Get some rest.
Jun.
Blue Cop!
Jun. Summon me, please.
But...
Please.
Well, alright.
Metal Breath, pickup!
Blue Cop, setup!
Ha! You again?
As long as there is a need to fight for justice, I will rise up time and time again!
Wow, how heroic!
Shadow X can't fly anymore.
Now's your chance to close in on him and take him down.
Roger that.
You thought that would keep me from flying? Ha!
Here we go!
Yahoo!
No way...
He could do that?
Haha! Coming through!
Woah! Not bad!
Now I'll show you something fun!
Heli-Tornado!
Jun! Are you alright?
I'm okay, don't worry!
Just hang in there. Let's get out of here for now.
Trust me on this! Friends believe in each other.
Friends...
I know you can do this!
Turn into a police car and run laps around him!
Got it!
What are you trying to do?!
Blue Cop's police car mode has less air resistance,
so it's not as easily affected by the wind!
That piece of-!
Just a little more! Faster!
Wha-! What's happening?!
He must consume a lot of energy to create a tornado that big!
He can't keep that up for long!
His system is overloaded!
Get him now, Blue Cop!
Megabolt Punch!
Megabolt...
Punch!
Aaaaah!
No way... my Heli-Tornado...
You did it, Blue Cop!
A true friend is someone who doesn't give up, even when things get tough.
Someone you can count on.
Friend? Heh.
Was that... what I didn't have?
I lost. As promised,
I will become your underling.
Not an underling. But a friend.
Sealing complete!
Good job.
But what are you going to do now?
Whaddya mean?
Have you forgotten? We're going live tonight.
Oh no!
So you see? All the robot sightings were actually made up
using custom made miniatures and special effects!
Hey, hang on!
We really saw it! It was a robot as big as a house, and flying around!
Oh, that?
Well, take a look!
Ahem. This robot is a 1 to 1 scale model made to order by a film studio.
What?! A model?!
Of course! It's made of styrofoam, so it's very light, you see? Heheh.
I put it in the warehouse, but it must have blown away in the wind.
I'm sorry for the commotion.
So everyone, this was our live broadcast,
"I Saw Mysterious Robots Flying Around the Docks!"
Make sure to tune in to our next episode!
And please remember to subscribe!
Urgh... do you think you can fool me with those lies?
I'll get my hands on some evidence no matter what it takes! You better watch out, Jun!